

Bharat Kumar

Cell Number: +92 342 0268814 Email: rajabarath39@gmail.com

Address: Muhammabad gate near Kala Pool NMC Center

Karachi

Summary

I'm a self-made driven individual, with knowledge of Computer Software with a focus on web based and Client- Server applications. I've developed **Web Application** in **Laravel** and **WordPress Projects**. I'm passionate about technology, and I pay meticulous attention to detail and problem-solving. I enjoy participating in continuous improvement efforts within the organization I work in.

I have 2.5 plus year experience.

Educational Qualification

Bachelors in Computer Science – 2015 to 2018 University of Sindh, Jamshoro

Skills

Programming Languages & web design: PHP -Word Press, Laravel, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, AJAX,

¡Query, Bootstrap

Application Server: XAMPP & WAMPP.

System Design: UML (Unified Modeling Language)

Code Development IDE: Dreamweaver 6 & 7, Sublime, Visual Studio Code, Notepad++

Operating Systems: Windows 10 Professional

Databases: MySQL

Professional Experience

Responsibilities:

- Development web application from scratch using PHP, MySQL, JQuery, AJAX, HTML5 & CSS3.
- Customization the WordPress themes.
- Developed small scale web application
- Identify bugs in web application and fixed them
- Write and modify database of web application
- Developed large and small scale web/database applications
- Actively utilize and manage front-end development with client-side validation and serverside
- Designed, developed, implemented, and tested changes

Company: O technology Pvt ltd

June 2021 to Continue ..

Description: Q technology is a multinational digital US based IT company in Pakistan. Q technology is an innovative experienced & highly professional IT outstanding company based in Pakistan.

I have many Project done here

Website: https://technado.co

Company: <u>Technado Pvt ltd</u> July 2021 to June 2022

Description: Technado is a multinational IT company in Pakistan. Technado is an innovative experienced & highly professional IT outstanding company based in Pakistan.

I have many Project done here

Website: https://technado.co

Company: Mean3 Pvt ltd August 2020 to July 2021

Description: Mean 3 Pvt Ltd as an information service provider with the aim to deliver business solution to people worldwide. They have many clients in worldwide and also own product

Website: https://www.mean3.com

Company: Brainiac Studio Pvt Ltd.

January 2020 to July 2020

Description: Brainiac Studio has IT as well as Marketing department; they have their own product named Big Owner which provides plots services in different cities of Pakistan Qatar. I have contribution in Big Owner.

Website: https://www.brainiac.studio

Projects I have done many projects.

https://helpinghandsadapt.org(Helping Hands Adapt)https://lyrikelgenius.com(Lryikegenious Game Api)https://nicnatpittypat.com(Nicnatpttypat Game Api)https://zarteam.org/admin(Zuni Admin Panel)

https://tenlittletoes.co/
https://kornholekings.com/
https://eximcentral.com/
https://kidocop.com/
https://kidocop.com/
https://data-matique.com/
(Zum Admin Panel)
(Kennholekings)
(Kornholekings)
(Exim Central Global)
(Kidocop Game Api
https://data-matique.com/
(Data Matique)